dubli.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy | DubLi - Better Deals, More Cashback

Effective Date: March 22, 2012 

**Data Processing Position**  
The responsible position for data processing is DUBLICOM Ltd. (Hereafter defined as DubLi including the website [www.dubli.com](http://www.dubli.com/).) Further details about the responsible position may be found in the imprint.

DubLi has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy statement and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  The TRUSTe program covers the website [www.dubli.com](http://www.dubli.com/) and does NOT cover information that may be collected through downloadable software on the site.   TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy statement or practices, please contact us at [privacy@dublinetwork.com](mailto:privacy@dublinetwork.com) If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

**Usage**  
We make use of your data in the processing of your order and to provide a free newsletter and information about special DubLi campaigns such as our sweepstakes. To opt out of these marketing emails, please follow the directions in the emails or use your account settings page to set your communications preferences. Customer data is stored and processed according to the "The Processing of Personal Data (Protection of Individuals) Law 138(I)2001 as amended by The Processing of Personal Data (Protection of Individuals) (Amendment) Law of 2003 (37(I)2003)". Until such time that this is cancelled, we will use your email address to send you our newsletters.  
****

**Information**  
We collect the following personal data such as, gender, first name, last name, postal address, country, phone number, username and password. You have the right, at any time, to free information, authorization, deletion or suspension of your personal data. Please use our ticket system at "Contact" to contact our support or send us your inquiry by mail or fax. Deletion requests cannot always be honored because of trading and taxation storage limit rules. Where appropriate, the suspension of data is valid in such cases.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please contact us.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address.  We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site.  DubLi stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

Your friend may contact us at [privacy@dublinetwork.com](mailto:privacy@dublinetwork.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

**We do not knowingly collect personal information from children.**  
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you believe a child has provided personal information to us, please contact us so that we can identify and delete that child's personal information.

**Disclosure of data to third parties**  
We do not provide your personal data (including home address or email address) to third parties without your expressed and, at any time, revocable permission. Exceptions are only made for our service partners who require such data in order to complete an order process (eg. A transport company responsible for shipping and a credit institute responsible for payment). In this case, transferred data is reduced to a minimum.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

**Security**  
The security of your personal information is important to DubLi.  When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can contact us at [security@dublinetwork.com](mailto:security@dublinetwork.com)

**Tracking Technologies**  
Cookies are used to store data about the contents of your shopping cart that can be accessed when you next visit the site. When you log in or make a purchase on our site, we require your customer data. The data contained in cookies allows you to avoid filling out forms at every site access. The cookies produced have a maximum expiration period of six months. Furthermore, you may use your browser program to manage or deactivate cookies produced on this page.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

**Use of data by Google** **  
** This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”).  Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage.  Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.  You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.  By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

**Social Media (Features) and Widgets**

Our Website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.

**Product Testimonials**

Our Website offers publicly accessible reviews. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our reviews, please contact us at [privacy@dublinetwork.com](mailto:privacy@dublinetwork.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Links to Other Websites   **

Our website includes links to other Websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of DubLi. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Website you visit.

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Information**

DUBLICOM Ltd.  
17 Gr. Xenopoulou Street  
3106 Limassol  
Cyprus
